var questions = [{
  question: 'Who was the sith that made the rule of two?',
  choices: ['Darth Bane', 'Darth Tyranus', 'Darth Vader', 'Darth Siddius'],
  answer: 'Darth Bane'
}, {
  question: 'What is Anakin Skywalker\'s mother\'s name?',
  choices: ['Leia', 'Gunga', 'Claire', 'Shimi'],
  answer: 'Shimi'
}, {
  question: 'Who was the Supreme Chancellor before Palpatine?',
  choices: ['Hedwig', 'Valurom', 'Gesso', 'Lena'],
  answer: 'Valurom'
}, {
  question: 'How old was Yoda when he died?',
  choices: ['900', '9000', '90', '500'],
  answer: '900'
}, {
  question: 'What was Luke Skywalker\'s original planned name?',
  choices: ['Bruce Globetrotter', 'Fry Farnsworth', 'Annikin Starkiller', 'Dash Rendar'],
  answer: 'Annikin Starkiller'
}, {
  question: 'What is Wedge\'s call sign?',
  choices: ['Red Leader', 'Yellow One', 'Yellow Two', 'Red Two'],
  answer: 'Red Two'
}, {
  question: 'Who is in charge of the original Death Star',
  choices: ['Boba Fett', 'Emperor Palpatine', 'Grand Moff Tarkin', 'Darth Vader'],
  answer: 'Grand Moff Tarkin'
}, {
  question: 'What planet does Yoda live on?',
  choices: ['Dagobah', 'Yavin', 'Bespin', 'Endor'],
  answer: 'Dagobah'
}, {
  question: 'Which of these is not a bounty hunter?',
  choices: ['Dengar', 'BT-987', 'IG-88', '4-LOM'],
  answer: 'BT-987'
}, {
  question: 'Who is Lando\'s co-pilot?',
  choices: ['Wedge Antilles', 'Biggs Darklighter', 'Nien Numb', 'Chewbacca'],
  answer: 'Nien Numb'
}];
